# Herry Herdianto

# **Senior Programmer**

# **Herry Herdianto**

Jl. Gadang Gg. XIB / 41B Malang, Jawa Timur, 65149

#### 081555600185

hherdianto@gmail.com

Highly-skilled software development professional bringing more than 20 years in software design, development and integration. Advanced knowledge of Java and PHP programming languages and Linux Administrator. Handled more than 50 application development projects as senior programmer at current institution or as freelancer.

#### **Skills**

Java (JSE, JEE & android) Excellent PHP & Laravel Excellent Linux Administrator Very Good Kotlin Very Good Javascript, node.js, Angular Very Good Python Very Good ElasticSearch Good C# Good **English Communication** Excellent **Bug Tracking** Excellent Database Design Excellent **Business Analysis** Good

## **Experience**

#### Mebiso.com / CTO

July 2022 - PRESENT, Malang, Jawa Timur

- Full Stack developer
- Coordinating with IT team
- Product Research and development
- Provide dedicated coaching to interns
- Develop high availability high scalability web application with micro services

#### BisnisOn.com / CTO

July 2018 - PRESENT, Malang, Jawa Timur

- Full Stack developer
- Managing all IT staffs
- Product Research and development
- Provide dedicated coaching to interns and new employees
- Develop code fixes and enhancements for inclusion in future code releases and patches

#### Gerakan Nasional 1000 Startup Digital / Facilitator - Hacker

ToT, Design Sprint, Speaker, Facilitator

2017 - 2020, Malang, Jawa Timur

#### STIE Malangkucecwara / Senior Programmer

July 2002 - PRESENT, Malang, Jawa Timur

- Implemented process management system using Java (JSE, JEE), PHP, Javascript language.
- Worked closely with clients to establish problem specifications and system designs.
- Provide dedicated coaching to interns and new employees.
- Designed and developed databases and analytical data structures.
- Developed code fixes and enhancements for inclusion in future code releases and patches.
- Remedied bug reports and handled other user issues quickly.
- Maintained existing applications and designed and delivered new applications.
- Modified existing software to correct errors, adapt to new hardware and improve performance.
- Made recommendations regarding information technology infrastructure overhauls.
- Established network specifications and analyzed workflow, access, information and security requirements.

# **Education**

### **STIE Malangkucecwara / S2**

September 2018 - Current, Malang, Jawa Timur

Postgraduate program, Financial Management

# Universitas Gadjah Mada / S1

July 1996 - July 2001, Jogjakarta, Jawa Tengah

Undergraduate program, Mathematics & Computer Science